（男鹿）これ以上　オレの周りを
ウロチョロして→
Just try and hang around
near me and act like a pain.
目障りな真似してみろ
後悔すんのはテメーの方だ。
You're the one who'll regret it!
久々に全開だ　ベル坊！
（ベル坊）ダーッ！
Let's go all out, for a change, Baby Beel!
（霧矢）ヒッ…やめ…。
ゼブルブラスト！
Zebel Blast!
（霧矢）ギャーッ！
うわ～っ！
ギャーッ！
（邦枝）な…！
（早乙女）なつかしいな…。→
This brings back memories.
フーッ。
（早乙女）ウチの問題児どもは
元気に暴れてるかな？
I wonder if that problem-child of mine
is having a good time goin' wild...
♪～　アーダダ　ダー
アイアイアイ…
アイーッ！
ダーブダー！
♪～　ダーダダ　アイアイアイ
ウイーッ
んだよ　ベル坊。
やけに御機嫌じゃね～か。
What's up, Baby Beel? You're
on cloud nine today...
ダダダ　アイーッ！
ダーッ！ダーブダッ！
俺にも歌えってか？
ウイーッ！
You want me to sing, too?
「ウイーッ！」じゃね～よ！
歌うか　ボケッ！
"Whee!!" my butt! I ain't singing, dork!
アイアイアイ…
ダーッ！ダーッ！
ウイ～ッ！イーヤッ！
ったく…ヒルダのやつ…。
Man...
Damn you, Hilda...
（出馬）((アカンで…悪魔の力→
You can't go showing your
demon power that much...
あんまり見せびらかしたら))
ダーダ！アイアイ。
《結局　あのメガネは
何もんなんだよ…→
Who the hell is that four-eyes, anyway?
説明もせずに
どっか行きやがって…》
ダーダ　アイアイ！
He split out of there without
explaining anything.
《つうか　そもそも侍女悪魔として
の仕事は　ど～なってんだ？→
And what about her job as Demon Maidservant?!
今朝なんかベル坊の世話
全部オレがやったんだぞ！→
I had to do everything for Baby
Beel this morning all on my own!
育児放棄か　このやろう！》
Did the bitch abandon him or what?
ウイーッ！
だから…。
I told you... I ain't singin'!
歌わねえっつってんだろ！
（邦枝）はあ…。
やっぱり怪しいわよね…。
Something's definitely odd...
（寧々）姐さん…
何やってるんすか？
Madame Aoi...
Whatcha doing, huh?
（由加）オニ怪しいっすよ？
You're actin' crazy strange!
な　なんでもない！
まさか　姐さん→
Nothing!
Don't tell me you're finally
gonna confess to Oga-chi, right?
と～と～男鹿っちに
告るつもりっすか？
（邦枝）は～？
ダメっすよ　姐さん！
私は認めませんからねっ！
No, you can't! I don't accept him yet!
ちが～うっ！
That's not it!
That Man Was a Teacher!
（生徒達の話し声）
（早乙女）いやはや　あちこち
回ってはきましたが→
Oh, my... I've been around in my day,
いいもんですなあ
日本の学校というのは。
but you just can't beat Japanese schools.
（教師）誰ですか？あれ…。
Who is that?
（教師）
校長のお知り合いだとか…。
An acquaintance of the Principal.
（教師）せ　先生…ですかね？
A-A teacher, right?
（早乙女）
特に制服がたまりませんなぁ。
Especially the uniforms...
I can't get enough of them.
あ～子連れ番長だ！
It's the Baby on Board Brawler!
手品　面白かったですよ～！
Those magic tricks were really something!
ベールちゃん　おかし食べる？
アダーッ！
Beel-chan, want a candy?
（古市）いやぁ　一時は
ど～なるかと思ったけど→
Well, I wasn't sure how things'd go for a
bit, but Baby Beel's identity seems to be safe.
ベル坊の正体も
バレてね～みたいだし→
一件落着だな。アダッ！
All's well that ends well.
ほら　お前も手ぇ振れって。
うっせ～な。
Come on, wave those hands!
Shut up. I ain't in the mood.
オレは今
それどころじゃね～んだよ。
あのメガネが　どういうつもりか
聞き出さね～と…。
I gotta ask what that four-eyes was up to.
（女子生徒）あの～。
あん？
にゃ？
Um...
ちょっと
お願いがあるんですけど～。
We have a little favor to ask...
ん？
んっ？
（寧々）
確かに昨日の試合で　男鹿の奴は
頑張ってましたけど…。→
It's true that Oga helped a lot
during the volleyball match,
でも！それだけで　あいつのことを
認められるってわけ…。
だから！
but that's not enough for me to accept...
I told you!
そういうんじゃないってば！
ただ　私は→
It's not like that, okay?
I just don't think all that fuss
yesterday was some trick is all!
昨日の騒ぎが手品とは
思えないってだけで…。
（男子生徒）
おい　子連れ番長が
手品　見せてくれるらしいぞ！
Hey, seems like the BoB Brawler
is doing more magic tricks!
（男子生徒）
マジで！？またイリュージョンか？
えっ！？
Seriously? Another illusion?
まさか　また昨日みたいに…。
Don't tell me... Like what
happened yesterday...
（ざわめき）
手品なんか　できるわけねぇだろ…
言やい～じゃねぇか。
I can't do any damn magic tricks!
Just tell 'em that!
昨日のは手品でも
なんでもね～って。
あほっ！
Tell 'em that yesterday wasn't some trick.
Idiot! If you admit your Demon powers
or whatnot in front of all these people,
こんな大勢の前で　悪魔とか何とか
馬鹿正直に言って→
また変な騒ぎになったら
ど～すんだ！→
you'll create another scene, and then what?
つ～か　信じるわけねえだろっ！
And anyway, they wouldn't believe you!
じゃあ　無視すりゃいいだろ～が。
アイ。
Then how about we ignore them?
女子のお願いを無下にする気か！
お前な…。
You wanna turn down the
request of a young lady?!
Look here, you...
とにかく　何かてきと～にだな…。
はあ…。
Anyway! Just do something. Whatever.
わあったよ。
ん？
'Kay.
え？ああっ！
オラオラオラオラ！
イリュージョン！
（古市）あ～～っ！！
Illusion!
（女子生徒）
キャーッ　飛んだわ！
あり得ないくらい飛んだわ！
He flew! He flew farther
than I could even imagine!
（男子生徒）すげえ！
イリュージョーン！
Wow! Illusion!
いつもの暴力でしょうが。
ん！？
Except it's just his usual violence...
（男子生徒）お～　もっかい見てえ。
（女子生徒）またやって…。
あの　すみません。
Um, excuse me...
（出馬）邦枝さんか。なんや？
Kunieda-san, is it?
What's up?
ちょっと聞きたいことがあって…
昨日の騒ぎなんですけど。→
I have something I need to ask.
It's about what happened yesterday.
あれって
どういうことなんですか？
What was that?
言うたやろ　イリュージョンやって。
手品や　手品。→
I told you, it was an illusion.
Just a trick, that's all.
Oga-kun helped me out with it.
男鹿くんに協力してもらってな。
（邦枝）
とてもそうとは思えませんでした。
I don't think that's what it was at all.
先輩は　男鹿とあの赤ん坊について
何か知ってるんじゃないですか？
You know something about Oga-kun
and that baby, don't you Senpai?
フッ。なんや　邦枝さん→
What's this, Kunieda-san? Are
you that interested in Oga-kun?
そない男鹿くんのことが
気になるんか？
えっ…いや
そういうんじゃなくてですね→
No, that's not it, see...
ただ　彼の正体を
知りたいというか…。
I just want to know who he really is, and...
（寧々）姐さん…。
Madame Aoi...
（由加）
そんなに外堀埋めないでも→
I think Oga-chi would say yes even
without all the prep-work, you know.
男鹿っちはオッケーすると
思うっスよ。
だ　だから　そ～いうんじゃ
ないって言ってるでしょ！
I'm telling you that's not how it is!
（チャイム）
勘のええ子や…さて
当の本人は　どうするんかいな。
That girl has good instincts.
But what will he do himself?
（東条）≪静！≫
Shizuka...
（静）あなたの方から声をかけて
くるなんてね…虎。→
I never thought you'd seek me out, Tora.
てっきり学校では　他人のフリを
つき通すのかと思ってたわ。
I thought we would continue to act like
we didn't know each other at school.
あいつの教室を教えてくれ　静。
あいつ？
Tell me what classroom he's in, Shizuka.
He?
あのメガネだ。オレのケンカはまだ
何も終わっちゃいねえ…。
The one with the glasses.
Our fight ain't over yet.
Teachers' Office
（教師）大変だ！屋上でまた
石矢魔の生徒がっ！
We've got trouble!
Those Ishiyama kids are
at it again on the roof!
（教師）また？
（教師）昨日の今日だぞ。
Again?
And right after yesterday...
警察を呼ぶか？
Should we call the police?
（早乙女）屋上って…→
The roof?
この上ですか？
You mean, above where we are?
（出馬）ふむ。君が来るとは
思っとったけど…→
I figured that you'd come.
そちらさんも来るとはなあ…。
えらいタイミングやんか。
But I didn't think you'd join in...
Good timing, you have.
東条　てめえ　すっこんでろ。
オレはこいつに話があんだよ。
Tojo... Stand the hell back.
Me and him got things to talk about.
後にしろ　男鹿。
邪魔すんなら　お前からつぶすぞ。
Do it later, Oga.
Get in my way, and I'll beat you first.
ガルルル…。
つまらんことでケンカしいな。
Don't go arguing about stupid things.
２人まとめて
かかってきたらええやんか。
Both o' you can come at me at once.
（男鹿・東条）はっ　上等だっ！
Fine by me!
（早乙女）よお　お前ら
ホームルームの時間だぞ。
Hey, people.
It's time for homeroom!
あ　あんたは…。
You're...
（男鹿・出馬・東条）うわ～っ！
ビエエエエエ！
（板書する音）
（ざわめき）
（早乙女）と　いうわけだ。
There you have it.
Saotome Zenjuro
今日からお前らの担任になる
早乙女だ。
I'm gonna be your homeroom
teacher starting today.
Name's Saotome.
（佐渡原）ほ　ほんとうですかっ？→
Principal's Office
R-Really?
You're saying I'm not assigned
to Ishiyama any more?
私が石矢魔の担当から
外れるというのは…。
Yes... Actually this is
how I always planned it.
（校長）うん。もともと　こ～ゆ～
決定だったんじゃ。→
You were just a stopgap until he came.
君は彼が来るまでの
つなぎのような感じで…。→
Sorry, I forgot to mention that.
すまんの　言うのを忘れておった。
Oh, no! Not a problem at all!
（佐渡原）いえ　とんでもないです！
（校長）君　うれしそうじゃな？
You seem happy about this.
W-Well...
（佐渡原）そっ　そんなことは！
と　ところで→
B-By the way, what is he
like, this new teacher?
どんな方なんですか？
新任の先生は。
（校長）風来坊じゃが
なかなかの人物じゃよ。→
A bit of a drifter, but really something.
早乙女禅十郎→
Saotome Zenjuro.
A legendary teacher who graduated
from Ishiyama High School.
石矢魔高校の卒業生にして
伝説の教師。
どうした～。
What the matter?
（早乙女）元気ね～ぞ～！この→
You guys seem down in the dumps!
You pieces of crap!
くそったれどもが。
はっはっはっは。
Um...
（邦枝）あの…担任が変わるとか→
We didn't hear anything about
having a new teacher...
私たち　何も聞かされて
ないんですけど…。
ん～…お前　名前は？
What's your name?
（邦枝）え…邦枝です。
そうか…。
Kunieda.
I see. You're a cute piece of crap.
（早乙女）可愛いな　くそったれ。
あ？
Got a boyfriend?
（早乙女）彼氏いんのか？
はあ～っ！？
Hold it there, bub!
おいコラッ！
Yer actin' pretty damn familiar
with Madame Aoi there, punk!
（寧々）てめえ　うちの姐さんに
ずいぶん慣れ慣れしい口→
きいてくれんじゃね～か！
（涼子）
セクハラで訴えられて～のか
このエロ教師！
You wanna get sued for
sexual harassment, Teach?
（早乙女）特攻服か…なつかしいな。
Gang clothes, huh? That sure
brings back memories...
Hands off!
触んなっ！
Why, you...
（涼子）てめえ！
はっ。
（早乙女）はっはっはっは！
元気じゃね～か。
Looks like you've got some spunk after all!
ほら　他の奴も
言いたいことあったら→
Look, if anyone else has something to say,
溜め込まずに　しっかり
殴りかかってこいよ？→
don't just sit there, come at me swingin'!
You're in high school! Nothing good'll
come from just sittin' there quietly!
高校生にもなって
行儀良く座ってても→
何にもなんね～ぞ　くそったれ。
はっはっはっは！
You pieces of crap!
Is this guy really a teacher?
ぶ～っ。
ふ～っ。
Saotome-sensei!
（邦枝）早乙女先生。
ん？
男鹿くんのことなんですけど…
何かあったんですか？
It's about Oga-kun... Did something happen?
ああ？
（邦枝）いえ　ボロボロに
なっていたので…。
Well, he's kind of all beat up.
ヒイイ～ッ！
ん～　ラブコメだな。
はっ？
Romantic comedy, is it?
男鹿が気になんのか？
You interested in Oga?
T-That's not it, see...
（邦枝）
だ　だから　そ～いうんじゃ…。
（寧々）じ～…。
（由加）うひひひ…。
ああ…。
あ～っ　もういいです！
Enough!
Madame, where are you going?
あ　姐さん！どこ行くんです？
（邦枝）自分で調べる！
I'll do my own investigating!
は～？
ぷ～。
ぶ～い～。
アイアイアイ！
ヒィー！アダアダ。
ブ～ダッ！
アダァーッ！
（ガダダン！）
Where am I?
ここはどこっ？
ワッチャネイム！？
What's yer name?!
フ～ッ。
（涼子・千秋・古市）おお～。
そうか…。そういやオレ
妙なおっさんに殴られて…。
I see.
Now that you mention it, I was
punched by some crazy old dude.
やっぱそうか…。
As we figured.
ぐ…　何なんだ　あの野郎…。
What the hell was with that guy? I'd
never taken a punch that powerful...
あんな重いパンチ
初めて食らったぞ…。
Plus, that guy's our homeroom teacher now.
（古市）しかも　そのおっさん
オレらの担任らしい。
担任？
Teacher?
（古市）ああ。
お前　気失ってただろ？→
Right. You were unconscious.
お前と東条を
かついで入ってきた時は→
When he brought you and Tojo
in, it shocked everyone.
全員　度肝抜かれたぞ。
ん？そういや東条は？
And where is Tojo?
（姫川）気がつくなり出てったぜ。
He left when he came to.
（神崎）そうとう　くやしかったん
じゃね～の？
Guess he couldn't take it.
くそっ　いねえ…。
（静）虎っ！
Shit, he ain't here!
Tora!
I heard.
聞いたわよ。出馬くんも男鹿くんも
やられたんですって？
Izuma-kun and Oga-kun were both beaten, too?
（東条）ああ。
それって　もしかして…。
Yeah...
Then could it be...
禅さんだ。
It's Zen-san.
間違いねえ。
Can't be anyone else.
He's... come back!
帰って…来たんだ…。
くそったれが…→
The pieces of crap did
a really number here...
派手にやってくれたな。
As I thought... It really is singed...
やっぱり…本当に焦げてる。
手品にしては　大掛かりすぎるわ。
This is way too big a scale for some trick.
次元に穴が空いてやがる。
They even opened up a dimensional hole.
（早乙女）
こいつがなけりゃ
この学校は消し飛んでたわけだ。→
Without this, the whole school
would've been blown away.
Not sure they knew or not,
知ってか知らずか
物理的ダメージを→
but it's a counter-reaction that minimized
the extent of the physical damage.
最小限におさえた反動だな…。
He's messed up, but he's still a demon lord.
（早乙女）まったく…腐っても
魔王じゃね～か。
まあ１０％ってとこか…。→
I guess 10%'ll do.
人間でも強い奴は感じちまうかも
しれね～が　仕方ねえ。
Strong humans might be able to
sense it, but I got no choice.
Whether it's a Demon or a serpent,
when I open up this box, all comers...
鬼が出るか蛇が出るか…
箱を開けてみんことにゃ…なっ！
あ…。
ダッ！
あ？
（アランドロン）むっ！？
What's with you, old man?
なんだよ　おっさん。
動くなっつってんだろ。
I told ya not to move!
あ　これは失礼しました。
Oh, pardon me.
I really don't like this model...
てゆ～か…このモデル嫌だ。→
We told you not to move!
だから動くなって！
ハァハァハァ…。
（邦枝）ハッ…なに？
What's that?
Above there?
この上に？
Looks like I got a cute Demon
Maidservant coming for me again...
こいつはまた　可愛い
侍女悪魔ちゃんが来たもんだ。
Fiend... Are you an agent of Behemoth?
（ヒルダ）
貴様…ベヘモットの手の者か。
（早乙女）あん？
（早乙女）おいおい
いきなり何すん…→
Hey, now! What do you think
you're doing all of a sud-
だっ！
Don't dodge the question.
とぼけるな。戯れに　こんなことを
する者など　そうはおらん。
No one would do something
like this just for fun.
先に断っておくぞ。坊っちゃまに
危害を加えるつもりなら→
Just to warn you...
If you intend harm to the young Master,
今ここで　とどめを刺す。
I will strike you down right here!
Really, Miss? White?
何だ　お嬢ちゃん…白か。
うっ！
あ～あ　くそったれ。
せっかく直したのによぉ。
You damn piece of crap... I just fixed that.
I think you're misunderstanding
something, Miss.
何か勘違いしてんじゃねえか
お嬢ちゃん。
I didn't come here to pick a fight with you.
オレは別に　あんたがたに
ケンカ売りにきたわけじゃ…。
So be it.
よかろう。
おいおい　くそったれ…
魔言召喚する気か？こんな所で。
Whoa, there! You're going to do
a Demonword Summon right here?
（邦枝）はっ　はっ　はっ…。
What's... that?
（邦枝）何？…あれ。
消えろ。
Begone.
いてて…。
That hurt, you piece of crap!
いてえじゃないか　くそったれ…
って　おいおい。
Whoa, there...
Fool, you want to blow
away the entire gymnasium?
バカが。
体育館ごとふっとばす気か。
あっ！
この上だな。
It's up there.
お前も気になるか？
ベル坊。
あ～い。
You curious too, Baby Beel?
Impossible...
バカな…。
Spellmaster...
スペルマスター…。
Plus that's... the Royal Crest!
しかも貴様…
それは王家の紋か？
わりいな。
しばらくは動けね～ぜ。→
Sorry, but you won't be
able to move for a while.
それ。
くっ…。
（早乙女）
ハッハッハ
落ち込むな　落ち込むな。→
Don't feel so down on yourself!
I think you were pretty strong for a
Demon Maidservant not under contract.
未契約の侍女悪魔にしちゃあ
強かったと思うぜ。→
Oh, right... Let me give you a warning.
ああ　そうだ。
一つ忠告しといてやる。→
The young Master and that
bad-boy, Oga was his name?
お嬢ちゃんとこのヤンチャボーズ
男鹿とか言ったか？
They need to be careful.
気をつけた方がいいぜ。
さっさと強くなんねえと…→
If they don't get stronger,
and soon, they're gonna die.
死んじまうからな。
Piece of crap... My best
duds are all dirty now!
くそったれが。一張羅が
汚れちまったじゃね～か。
ん！？
フッ…。
待てよ。
Wait.
てめえ一体　何者だ？
Who the hell are you?
（早乙女）
ん～？決まってんじゃね～か。→
Isn't it obvious?
Your teacher.
先生だ。明日も学校来いよ。
くそったれ。
Come to school tomorrow, you piece of crap.
ああ～？
んなこと聞いてんじゃ…。
にょ。
That's not what I asked!
くっ。
（校長）どうだったかね？
蝿の王の末っ子は。
What do you think of the Lord
of Flies youngest child?
（早乙女）ん～　全然ダメっすわ。→
He's totally no good.
That's asking for trouble, isn't it?
あれはヤバいんじゃないっすかね。ま　忠告は一応しましたが。
Well, I did give them a warning.
来ると思うかね？
（早乙女）まあ　来るでしょうなあ。
You think he'll come?
Yeah, he probably will.
You can never tell with that guy.
あいつ　超テキトーだからなあ…。
Sounds like we've got a
new character next week!
And this time it's someone
from the Demon World!
Like, Angelica-san's big sister?
Lamia's older sister who happens
to be a beautiful nurse?!
Neither seems right.
Then who in the world is coming?
On the next Beelzebub: The
Sibling Rivalry Has Begun!
Sibling rivalry? Don't tell me
Alaindelon has an older brother?
You'd want that?
No, not at all.